<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Red on Pavel Konoplenko Home</title><link>https://pavelnovel.com/tags/red/</link><description>Recent content in Red on Pavel Konoplenko Home</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 10:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pavelnovel.com/tags/red/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Natural conversations</title><link>https://pavelnovel.com/posts/post-4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://pavelnovel.com/posts/post-4/</guid><description>&lt;p>There&amp;rsquo;s no perfect prompt, no perfect instruction, no perfect project spec. That&amp;rsquo;s not where the work is done. The prompts are the sentences, the memos, the emails to the team along the way. When we talk to the human, we don&amp;rsquo;t sit there to craft a perfect sentence before the words come out. We let them come out and we shape it how it comes, together in the conversation.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Real work is messy and undefined and unpredictable. Spending any time to craft a prompt is time wasted. We&amp;rsquo;ve got it in our heads that they need a good prompt. With enough iterations, a long chain of two-word prompts will outdo an excellent and laborious 2-shot prompt. And you yourself as the operator will gather way more insights along the way than the two responses.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Any day can be a big day</title><link>https://pavelnovel.com/posts/post-1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://pavelnovel.com/posts/post-1/</guid><description>&lt;p>I did something really cool today in building this website.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Rivers moving</title><link>https://pavelnovel.com/posts/post-3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 11:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://pavelnovel.com/posts/post-3/</guid><description>&lt;p>To watch a raindrow fall down a windschield&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&amp;hellip;is to see the river slither across the landscape.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Following obsessions</title><link>https://pavelnovel.com/posts/post-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://pavelnovel.com/posts/post-2/</guid><description>&lt;p>Knowing when is enough is the secret. There&amp;rsquo;s different levels of obsessions, all concurrently pulling and influences us.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We find ourselves in the middle.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>