<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Pavel Konoplenko Home</title><link>https://pavelnovel.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Pavel Konoplenko Home</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 00:53:52 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pavelnovel.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Two questions for writing</title><link>https://pavelnovel.com/posts/writing-questions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 00:53:52 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://pavelnovel.com/posts/writing-questions/</guid><description>&lt;p>Two questions were on my mind during the writing process.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Where’s the weird?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Are you being precious?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The first question focused me on exploring both the edges and the core, two places that paradoxically contain the most weird. And when you touch both the extremes and the core, you really are touching the whole thing and thus I was wholly me.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The second question was a challenge to not get stuck on one idea, one angle, one thought. There were always more thoughts coming around the corner. Ideas never come alone, they come together. If you&amp;rsquo;re precious with one idea and don&amp;rsquo;t let it breathe, you don&amp;rsquo;t know what ideas it was coming with. So I let the weird flow, becoming a real audience to my own writing. Not as a critic, but as a reader ready to follow where the ideas lead. That&amp;rsquo;s the editing side now.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Natural conversations</title><link>https://pavelnovel.com/posts/natural-conversations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://pavelnovel.com/posts/natural-conversations/</guid><description>&lt;p>There&amp;rsquo;s no perfect prompt, no perfect instruction, no perfect project spec. That&amp;rsquo;s not where the work is done. The prompts are the sentences, the memos, the emails to the team along the way. When we talk to the human, we don&amp;rsquo;t sit there to craft a perfect sentence before the words come out. We let them come out and we shape it how it comes, together in the conversation.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Real work is messy and undefined and unpredictable. Spending any time to craft a prompt is time wasted. We&amp;rsquo;ve got it in our heads that they need a good prompt. With enough iterations, a long chain of two-word prompts will outdo an excellent and laborious 2-shot prompt. And you yourself as the operator will gather way more insights along the way than the two responses.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Any day can be a big day</title><link>https://pavelnovel.com/posts/big-day/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://pavelnovel.com/posts/big-day/</guid><description>&lt;p>I did something really cool today in building this website.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Following obsessions</title><link>https://pavelnovel.com/posts/following-obsessions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://pavelnovel.com/posts/following-obsessions/</guid><description>&lt;p>Knowing when is enough is the secret. There&amp;rsquo;s different levels of obsessions, all concurrently pulling and influences us.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We find ourselves in the middle.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>